Dan Hakes

Botanical Services, LLC

West Bend, WI 53090 hakes469@gmail.com 262-893-7324

To further advance myself and others through hard work and a persistent integrity, while achieving the common goal

of growth and success, as well as personal growth in life and experience.

Worked at Botanical Services, LLC for the last 4 years and worked 2nd jobs listed below during that time.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

While Employed full-Time

Landscape Construction - Botanical Services, LLC January 2014 to Present

- Responsible for planning weekly schedules and work assignments.
- Developing customer relations, upselling services and maintaining project schedule.
- Assist in design process and quoting of work.

Machine Operator

RR Donnelley

March 2018 to May 2018

- Set up and operate folders, saddle stitchers and other offline equipment based on the needs of each job.
- Managed crew of 1 to 3 people.
- Responsible for quality of the finished project according to company standards.

Bindery Operator

Arandell Corp

October 2016 to June 2017

- Set up and maintain the quality, production and mechanical aspects of an SP-1000 saddle stitcher.
- Scheduling work flow and adjusting schedule to maintain on time delivery.

Shift Supervisor

Converting Technology, Inc May 2015 to October 2016

Production Supervisor

RJ Wood Industries

July 2014 to September 2015

Responsible for daily scheduling of employees and workload to ensure OTD. Starting a safety program and having the shop stocked with adequate safety items. Accountability with employees with regards to company

policies and procedures. Ensure deliveries were sent out on time to job sites. Inventory control and restocking of daily use items.

Set Up Technician

Converting Technology, Inc December 2014 to May 2015

• Completes production plan by scheduling and assigning personnel; accomplishing work results; establishing

priorities; monitoring progress; revising schedules and resolving problems.

 Accomplishes manufacturing staff results by communicating job expectations; planning, monitoring, and appraising job results; coaching, counseling, and disciplining employees; initiating, coordinating, and

enforcing systems, policies, and procedures.

- Maintains staff by training and developing personal growth opportunities.
- Maintains workflow by monitoring steps of the process; observing control points and equipment; monitoring

personnel and resources.

- Maintains quality output by enforcing organization standards.
- Ensures operation of equipment by calling for repairs.
- Provides manufacturing information by compiling, initiating, and sorting performance data; answering

questions and responding to requests.

• Maintains safe and clean work environment by educating and directing personnel on the use of all equipment.

and resources; maintaining compliance with established policies and procedures.

• Resolves personnel problems by analyzing data; investigating issues; identifying solutions; recommending

action.

Set Up Technician - Converting Technology, Inc December 2014 to May 2015

Working with the shift supervisor to set up the plastic converting machines based on the schedule and customer

needs. Set up additional secondary equipment as needed based on what was called out from each customer

specs. Included in line print stands, folders, integrity sealers and punches.

Production Supervisor

Compo Steel Products May 2014 to July 2014

Responsible for the productivity, quality, scheduling and employees of 2nd shift. This included employee evaluations,

goal setting and accountability. Working with HR for staffing levels and assisting in the functions of management.

Delivery Driver

Spee-Dee Delivery Inc

_

Pewaukee, WI

February 2014 to May 2014

Loading and organizing your vehicle based on the deliveries for your assigned route each day. Obeying traffic laws and courteous, customer service when making deliveries. Able to lift 100 pounds and complete a DOT physical

assessment, helping other drivers with assistance with LTL deliveries, making sure all the pick-ups on the route were

done daily, scanning each and every package for tracking information and working with customer service to expedite

a package or a pick-up for customers. Working OT as needed to ensure delivery of every package on your route.

Production Supervisor

Trans Coil Inc

_

Milwaukee. WI

June 2013 to November 2013

2nd shift Standard Division - Oversee the Safety, quality and production of the Standard Division. Includes scheduling,

hiring, maintaining the 97% OTD metric, cellular manufacturing process, employee rotation schedule to ensure cross

training, inventory control, GOAL setting for employees, maintaining Capacity Planning as it relates to scheduled work and labor hours as well as cell output capacity averages, upholding company policies and procedures, cost reduction

and change management.

Production Manager - SS Coaters, LLC

Super Steel, LLC

-

Milwaukee, WI

October 2012 to May 2013

Plan, organize and direct the manufacturing and maintenance operations which ensure the most effective return on assets.

Initiative plans and processes which minimize manufacturing costs through effective utilization of manpower, equipment,

facilities, materials, and capital. Assure attainment of business objectives and productions schedules while insuring product

standards that will exceed our customers' expectations. Implement manufacturing strategies and action plans to ensure

that the facility supports the company's strategic initiatives. Establish group and individual accountabilities throughout assigned departments for problem solving and cost reduction, both on a permanent and ad-hoc basis, depending on need.

Encourage use of new techniques and focus on fact based problem solving.

Production Supervisor

Advanced Coatings, Inc

-

West Bend, WI January 2007 to October 2012

Plan a production schedule, implement and control the production schedule, review and adjust the schedule where needed, manage human and material resources to meet production targets, make decisions about equipment use,

maintenance, modification and procurement, work out and implement standard operating procedures for production

operations, ensure that standard operating procedures are adhered to, ensure implementation and adherence to health and safety procedures, monitor quality standards of products, implement and enforce quality control and tracking

programs to meet quality objectives, determine and implement improvements to the production process, prepare and

maintain production reports, monitor and review the performance of staff and organize necessary interventions for improvement, estimate production costs, set production budgets, manage production budgets and implement cost control programs.

Lead Painter

Bucyrus International

_

Milwaukee, WI

September 2005 to January 2007

Provide leadership to the paint shop to keep production requirements on task. Lead 6 painters across multiple shifts to ensure delivery of finished product was kept on time by developing schedules, working with suppliers to manage

inventory of materials and working with other departments to keep product flowing.

Education

Psychology

University of Wisconsin Washington County West Bend

-

West Bend, WI 2004 to 2005

Northeast Wisconsin Technical College Green Bay

-

Green Bay, WI

1990